Lovestruck: The Musical is a comedy, fantasy,
romance film directed by Sanaa Hamri.
Harper was one of the best dancers to hit Broadway, but an injury caused her to leave
the spotlight, become a choreographer, and raise her daughter Mirabella.
When Mirabella decides to quit the show to get married, her mother is determined to put a stop
to the wedding and show Mirabella that she cannot give up her career for love.
Harper Hutton, played by Chelsea Kane.
Ryan Hutton, played by Drew Seeley.
Mirabella Hutton, played by Sara Paxton.
Ryan Hutton, played by Tom Wopat.
Harper Hutton, played by Jane Seymour.
Marco Vitturi, played by Alexander DiPersia.
Lovestruck: The Musical is an American romance jukebox musical
television film that premiered on April 21, 2013 on ABC Family.
The film is directed by Sanaa Hamri and produced by
Gaylyn Fraiche and Salli Newman.
It stars Drew Seeley, Chelsea Kane, Sara Paxton, Jane Seymour and Tom Wopat.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.